{
    "levels": [
        {
            "level1": [
                {
                    "question": "Does Plastic affect marine life?",
                    "choice1": "Marine species can digest it",
                    "choice2": "Marine species are improved",
                    "choice3": "Does not affect marine life",
                    "answer": "Marine species get tangled in it"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which contributes more to marine pollution?",
                    "choice1": "Food waste",
                    "choice2": "Household waste",
                    "choice3": "Death of aquatic organism",
                    "answer": "Pipes discharge waste in sea"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Oil pollution is worst because -",
                    "choice1": "Density",
                    "choice2": "volume",
                    "choice3": "Mass",
                    "answer": "Visibility"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How to reduce the pollution on ocean?",
                    "choice1": "Manual cleaning of pollutants",
                    "choice2": "Damping the pollutants during winter",
                    "choice3": "Ban the license of industries near sea",
                    "answer": "Introducing sewage treatment plants"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which is highest waste discharge to water?",
                    "choice1": "Spillage from oil pipelines",
                    "choice2": "Nuclear waste",
                    "choice3": "Spillage from tankers",
                    "answer": "Sewage"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level2": [
                {
                    "question": "What is recycling?",
                    "choice1": "Buying new clothes",
                    "choice2": "Throwing things in the garbage can",
                    "choice3": "Selling items",
                    "answer": "Reuse material to make new thing"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the 3 R’s?",
                    "choice1": "Redirect, Rude, Round",
                    "choice2": "Respectful, Responsible, Right",
                    "choice3": "Rewrite, Rewind, Respond",
                    "answer": "Reduce, Reuse, Recycle"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Household waste is recycled most in -",
                    "choice1": "Australia",
                    "choice2": "India",
                    "choice3": "China",
                    "answer": "Austria"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which does not go in compost heap?",
                    "choice1": "Coffee grounds",
                    "choice2": "Vacuum cleaner waste",
                    "choice3": "White paper bags",
                    "answer": "Meat Scraps"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the benefit of recycling?",
                    "choice1": "Reducing landfills",
                    "choice2": "Less pollution",
                    "choice3": "Fewer resources are taken from earth",
                    "answer": "All are True"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level3": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the major problem of Landfills?",
                    "choice1": "Running out of space for landfills",
                    "choice2": "Cannot hold enough garbage",
                    "choice3": "Smell bad",
                    "answer": "Emit toxins nd greenhouse gases"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which does not belong to landfill?",
                    "choice1": "Certain plastics",
                    "choice2": "Painted wood",
                    "choice3": "Old mattresses",
                    "answer": "Waste water"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does a landfill contain?",
                    "choice1": "Paper and plastic",
                    "choice2": "Things that cannot be recycled",
                    "choice3": "Recyclable dropped wrongly",
                    "answer": "All are True"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Landfill site should be chosen carefully cause -",
                    "choice1": "Farmers get annoyed",
                    "choice2": "People don’t like the smell",
                    "choice3": "None of the above",
                    "answer": "Water supplies will get contaminated"
                },
                {
                    "question": "One way to reduce landfill is?",
                    "choice1": "Reuse materials",
                    "choice2": "Recycle materials",
                    "choice3": "Avoid using packaging not needed",
                    "answer": "All are True"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}